Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
John Vliet Lindsay papers
1944-2001
MS 592
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
216.33
(485 boxes)
The papers, divided into two parts, document the life and political career of John Lindsay from student days at Yale University through his two terms as mayor of New York City, 1965-1973. Part I. contains pre-congressional and congressional papers covering the years 1944-1965 and includes his Yale senior thesis, personal correspondence and subject files, campaign records, and congressional papers for the years 1959-1965. Part II. contains Lindsay's personal mayoral papers covering the years 1965-1973. The papers include personal correspondence, schedules, appointment books, subject files, campaign records, the papers of ten assistants to the mayor, photographs and other materials. Accessions to the collection provide additional material relating to Lindsay's congressional and mayoral years, as well as his 1972 Democratic presidential nomination bid and his 1980 Senate primary campaign.
Lindsay, John V. (John Vliet), 1921-2000
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exists pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Separated Materials
Part II. Series XXV, boxes 435 and 436, RESTRICTED PERSONAL FINANCIAL RECORDS destroyed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of John V. Lindsay, 1973-1982; Allen Klotz, 1982 (Accessions 1983-M-009), Jay Kriegel, 1997 (Accession 1998-M-094), Katharine Lake, 2005, Ava Carberry, 2007 (Accession 2007-M-061), and Mrs. Anne P. Sidamon-Eristoff, 2014 (Accession 2014-M-053). Gift of Katharine Lake, 2016 (Accession 2016-M-075).
Arrangement
Arranged in two parts, oversize material, and seven additions: Part I. Pre-Congressional and Congressional Papers. Part II. New York City Mayoral Personal Papers.
Part I is organized into fourteen series: I. Yale College, 1944. II. Executive assistant to the U.S. Attorney General, 1954-1958. III. American Bar Association, 1950-1960. Personal correspondence, 1949-1961. V. Campaign records, 1958. VI. Appointment books, 1959-1965. VII. Bills introduced, 1959-1965. VIII. NATO Parliamentarian's Conference and Ditchley Foundation conference records, 1955-1965. IX. Policy file, chronological, 1958-1965. X. Policy file, by subject, 1958-1965. XI. Speech file, 1958-1965. XII. Constituent newsletters and questionnaires, 1959-1965. XIII. Publication reprints, 1959-1965. XIV. Biographical newspaper and magazine articles, 1959-1965.
Part II is organized into twenty-five series: I. Personal correspondence, 1966-1973. II. Schedules and fact sheets, 1965-1973. III. Appointment books and journals, 1965-1973. IV. Daily crisis calendars, 1970-1973. V. Speech files, 1966-1969. VI. Campaign records, 1965. VII. Campaign records, 1969. VIII. Presidential campaign, 1972. IX. National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968. X. Project management staff, 1972-1973. XI. Robert W. Sweet (Deputy Mayor), 1969. XII. Richard R. Aurelio (Deputy Mayor), 1969-1972. XIII. Edward Hamilton (Deputy Mayor), 1969-1973. XIV. Sid Davidoff (Assistant to the Mayor), 1965-1973. XV. Nathan Leventhal (Assistant to the Mayor), 1970-1972. XVI. Jay Kriegel (Assistant to the Mayor), 1966-1973. XVII. Constantine Sidamon-Eristoff (Assistant to the Mayor), 1966. XVIII. Steven Isenberg (Assistant to the Mayor), 1970-1973. XIX. Richard Weston (Assistant to the Mayor), 1972-1973. XX. Peter Goldmark (Assistant to the Mayor), 1965-1970. XXI. Photographs, 1950-1972. XXII. Audio material, 1965-1972. XXIII. Telephone conversation records: lists and memoranda, 1968-1973. XXIV. Campaign workers and fund raising records, 1958-1973. XXV. Restricted personal financial records, 1957-1971.
Scope and Contents
The papers, divided into two parts, document the life and political career of John Lindsay from student days at Yale University through his two terms as mayor of New York City, 1965-1973. Part I contains pre-congressional and congressional papers covering the years 1944-1965 and includes his Yale senior thesis, personal correspondence and subject files, campaign records, and congressional papers for the years 1959-1965. Part II contains Lindsay's personal mayoral papers covering the years 1965-1973. The papers include personal correspondence, schedules, appointment books, subject files, campaign records, the papers of ten assistants to the mayor, photographs and other materials. Accessions to the collection provide additional material relating to Lindsay's mayoral years, as well as his 1972 Democratic presidential nomination bid and his 1980 Senate primary campaign.
Biographical / Historical
John V. Lindsay: born on November 24, 1921, in New York City; lawyer, former mayor of New York City; B.A., Yale, 1944, LL.B., Yale Law School, 1948; law practice in New York City, 1949-; executive assistant to the United States Attorney General, 1955-1957; member of the United States House of Representatives, 86th-89th Congress, 17th District, New York, 1959-1965; Mayor of New York City, 1966-1973; vice chairman, National Commission on Civil Disorders, 1967. Died on December 19, 2000, in Hilton Head, South Carolina.
Law; Mayors -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.) -- History -- 1951-; Mayors -- New York (State) -- New York -- Elections; New York (N.Y.) -- Politics and government -- 1951-; United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1953; Lawyers; Mayors; Politicians; United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1989; Aurelio, Richard S.; Davidoff, Sidney; Goldmark, Peter C.; Hamilton, Edward; Isenberg, Steven; Kriegel, Jay L.; Leuenthal, Nathan; Lindsay, John V. (John Vliet), 1921-2000; Sidamon-Eristoff, Constantine, 1930-2011; Sweet, Robert; Weston, Richard
- Pre-Congressional and Congressional Papers, 1944-1965; Part I
  - Yale College, 1944; Series I
    - Senior thesis: "Religious Aspects in the Life and Times of Oliver Cromwell", 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Assistant to the U.S. Attorney General, 1954-1958; Series II
    - Application for position, correspondence and memoranda, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Affronti case, personal letters, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Supreme Court: Affronti v. U.S., and Jay v. Boyd, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Supreme Court: Jencks v. U.S., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Jenks case: memorabilia and clippings, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Resignation letter as Executive Assistant to U.S. Attorney General, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Department of Justice, Executive Reserve, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Bar Association, 1950-1960; Series III
    - Section on Antitrust Law, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bar admission, 1950-1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Conflict of Interest Law Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Family part of Supreme Court Committee, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets and notices, miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - City and state correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Trade Marks and Unfair Competition Committee, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    - Character and Fitness Committee, application to, 1949-1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Federal Legislation, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Certificate of admission to Court of Appeals, 2nd Circuit, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Criminal Courts, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of Executive Committee, correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16-21)
    - Treasurer's and offices' of Executive Committee reports, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 22-24)
    - Notices, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Resolution drafts, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
    - Memoranda and statistics, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 28-31)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1949-1961; Series IV
    - A-B, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - C-E, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - F-H, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - I-K, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - L, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - M, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - N-P, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - R, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - S, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - T-V, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - W-Z, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Berkshire Industrial Firm, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Congratulations re: partnership in Webster, Sheffield and Chrystie, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
    - Congratulations re: return to law practice, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
    - Congratulatory letters to friends and colleagues, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Jane Littleton, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Joseph Macchia, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lunch Club, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1959 (Box 9, Folder 23-26)
    - Personal, 1952-1962 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - St. Paul's alumni association, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Webster, Sheffield, Fleischman, Hitchcock and Chrystie partnership agreement, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Yale Development Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Young Republican Club, 1951-1959 (Box 10, Folder 32-35)
  - Campaign Records, 1958; Series V
    - Congratulatory correspondence (Box 11, Folder 1-7)
    - Congratulatory correspondence, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8-12)
    - Public appearance invitations (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Speech drafts and memoranda (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - Speech drafts and memoranda (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Primary election correspondence (Box 13, Folder 17-19)
    - Republican Club County Committee (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Staff appreciations (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Thank you letters to campaign workers (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Appointment Books, 1959-1965; Series VI
    - 1959-1962 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
    - 1963-1965 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5-8)
  - Bills Introduced, 1959-1965; Series VII
    - 86th Congress, 1st Session, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress, 2nd Session, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 87th Congress, 1st Session, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 87th Congress, 2nd Session, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 88th Congress, 1st Session, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 88th Congress, 2nd Session, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 89th Congress, 1st Session, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - NATO Parliamentarian's Conference and Ditchley Foundation Conference Records, 1955-1965; Series VIII
    - 1st thru 6th Parliamentarians' Conferences: memoranda and proceedings, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - 7th Parliamentarians' Conference: memoranda and proceedings, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 3-6)
    - 8th Parliamentarians' Conference: memoranda and proceedings, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 8th Parliamentarians' Conference: memoranda and proceedings, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - 9th Parliamentarians' Conference: memoranda and proceedings, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - 10th Parliamentarians' Conference: memoranda and proceedings, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Parliamentarians' Conference: correspondence, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
    - Parliamentarians' Conference: correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13-18)
    - Ditchley Foundation Conference, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Policy File, Chronological, 1958-1965; Series IX
    - 1959-1962 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 1-9)
    - 1962-1963 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 10-16)
    - 1964-1965 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
  - Policy File, By Subject, 1958-1965; Series X
    - Agriculture (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights (Box 24, Folder 3-6)
    - Economy in government (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Education and the arts (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Foreign affairs (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
    - Foreign affairs (Box 25, Folder 11-12)
    - Government organization and operation (Box 25, Folder 13-15)
    - Government regulations (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Housing and urban affairs (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
    - Immigration (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Judicial matters (Box 26, Folder 20-21)
    - Labor (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - National defense (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - New York matters (Box 26, Folder 25-26)
    - Political (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Political (Box 27, Folder 28-29)
    - Public works and conservation (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Social welfare (Box 27, Folder 31-32)
    - Taxation (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Tributes (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Veterans (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Speech File, 1958-1965; Series XI
    - Interview remarks, 1958-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Medicare, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - The national economy, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - "Right to Know", 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Foreign affairs, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Education, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - "Meet the Press", 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - New York Republican Club, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Drafts, miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 12-15)
  - Constituent Newsletters and Questionnaires, 1959-1965; Series XII
    - 1960-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1-22)
  - Publication Reprints, 1959-1965; Series XIII; .75 linear feet (2 boxes)
    - Congressional Record Reprints
      - "William M. Stucky, V.S. Citizen", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - "Foreign Tourist Travel", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - "Civil Rights", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - "Immigration Refugee Legislation", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - "Foreign aid", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - "Juvenile Delinquency", 1961 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - "The Fox Bill", 1962 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - "Trade Expansure Act of 1962" (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - "Our City's Need: Middle Income Housing", 1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - "Our National Fallout Policy", 1962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - "The Federal Government and the Arts", 1963 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - "Establishing National Advisory Council on Education", 1963 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - "A Special Duty for Republicans", 1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - "Atlantic Unity", 1963 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - "The Key to a Livelier GOP", 1963 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - "Amendments to Clean Air Act", 1965 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Magazine and newspaper articles
      - "The Cries of Our Cities," Progressive Architecture, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - "Still Millions of Refugees," New York, Times Magazine, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - "A Compelling Need: A Feasible Plan," Show Magazine, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - "Intellectual Freedom and the Federal Government," Publishers Weekly, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Forge of Democracy by Neil MacNeil reviewed by JVL, Herald Tribune, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - "Atlantic Parliamentary Assembly," New York/VSA, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - "Too Many People Have Guns," Saturday Evening Post, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - "An Inquiry into the Darkness of the Cloak, the Sharpness of the Dagger," Esquire, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - "A Special Duty for Republicans," Harper's, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - "Quit Bugging Us," Washington Post, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - "The New GOP," Atlantic Monthly, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - The Agony of the GOP by Robert Novak, reviewed by JVL, Washington Post, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - "A Congressman Looks at the Arts," Saturday Review, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - The Naked Society by Vance Packard and The Privacy Invaders by Myron Brenton, reviewed by JVL, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Biographical Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1959-1965; Series XIV
    - Addresses, 1965-1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, 1961-1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Air pollution, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Aldrich controversy, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Appearances, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
    - Civil rights, 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 7-9)
    - Congressional reform, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Conservation, 1962-1965 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Congressional election, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Congressional elections, 1960-1964 (Box 34, Folder 13-20)
    - Defense, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Elections and endorsements, 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 22-24)
    - Federal aid to education, 1958-1963 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Fine arts, 1959-1963 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Fire Island bill, 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Foreign affairs, 1962-1965 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Goldwater statement (refusal to endorse ticket), 1964 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - House Unamerican Activities Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Immigration, 1959-1964 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - JVL general biographical sketch, 1950-1965 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - JVL for higher office, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Judiciary, 1959-1964 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Labor, 1959-1965 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Lindsay, Mary, 1961-1964 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Medicare, 1961-1965 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Mayoralty candidacy, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 38-41)
    - Narcotics, 1960-1964 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - New York City local affairs, 1959-1965 (Box 36, Folder 43-45)
    - New York City local affairs, 1959-1965 (Box 37, Folder 46-49)
    - Nuclear fallout shelters, 1960-1963 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Politics as a career, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 51-52)
    - Presidential election, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Republican Party, 1959-1965 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - School intergration, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - School prayer issue, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Staff and interns, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Taxation, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Television and radio appearances, 1960-1965 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Unemployment, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Urban affairs and housing, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - War on Poverty program, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 63)
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Personal Correspondence, 1966-1973; Series I
    - A (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Ba-Bl (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Bo-Bu (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Ca-Ch (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Cl-Co (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Cr-Cu (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - D (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - E (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - F (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - G (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Hab-Han (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Har-Hay (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - He (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Ho (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Hu-Hy (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - I (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - J (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Ka-Ki (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Kl-Ky (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - La-Le (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Li-Ly (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Ma (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Me-Mi (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Mo-Mu (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - N (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - O (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - P (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Ra-Ri (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Rob-Roo (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Ros-Ru (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Sa-Sh (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Si-Sq (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - St (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Su-Sy (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Ta-Th (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Ti-Ty (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - U (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - V (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Wa (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - We (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Wh-Wy (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Y (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Z (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Schedules and Fact Sheets, 1965-1973; Series II
    - JVL Schedule, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - JVL Walking tours, Manhattan, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - JVL Walking tours, out of town, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - JVL Walking tours, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - JVL Walking tours, Staten Island, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Mayor's schedule (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - JVL Walking tours, Brooklyn, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - JVL Walking tours, Queens, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - JVL Walking tours, Bronx, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1968 May 3,16,31, July 2,15 (Box 43, Folder 10-14)
    - Schedule, official work week, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1968 September 13, December 17 (Box 43, Folder 16-17)
    - House gatherings, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1969 April 7 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - JVL public appearances
      - Workshop in business opportunities, 1969 January 8 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Association of the Bar, 1968 January 10 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1969 January 13 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Association of American Colleges, 1969 January 14 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Rotary International, 1969 January 15 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1969 January 16 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Bowdoin Alumni Association of New York, 1969 January 24 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Women's National Republican Club, Inc., 1969 January 25 (Box 43, Folder 27-28)
      - East Coast Regional Conference, 1969 January 30 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1969 January 31 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - JVL public appearances
      - State of New Jersey, Department of Community Affairs, 1969 February 4 (Box 43, Folder 31-32)
      - Franklin D. Roosevelt Four Freedoms Award, 1969 February 6 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1969 February 6 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - JVL public appearances
      - The Association of Towns of The State of New York, 1969 February 10 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Social Science Honor Society, 1969 February 10 (Box 43, Folder 36-37)
      - Kings County Republican County Committee, 1969 February 12 (Box 43, Folder 38-39)
      - New York Republican County Committee, 1969 February 15 (Box 43, Folder 40-41)
      - Guardian Association, 1969 February 16 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Republican Citizens Finance Committee of Indiana, 1969 February 18 (Box 43, Folder 43-44)
      - American College of Cardiology, 1969 February 27 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1969 February 28 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - JVL public appearances
      - Bronx Committee for Responsible Republican Action, 1969 February 28 (Box 43, Folder 47)
      - St. Patrick's Day parade, 1969 March 4 (Box 43, Folder 48)
      - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1969 March 5 (Box 43, Folder 49-50)
      - Municipal Bond Club of New York, 1969 March 5 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Scheduling meeting, 1969 March 10 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - JVL public appearances
      - Commerce and Industry Associates of New York, 1969 March 12 (Box 44, Folder 53)
      - Better Business Bureau, 1969 March 12 (Box 44, Folder 54)
      - Association of the Bar, 1969 March 12 (Box 44, Folder 55)
      - Educational alliance, 1969 March 16 (Box 44, Folder 56)
      - Society of Friendly Sons of St. Patirck, 1969 March 17 (Box 44, Folder 57-58)
      - Social Science Honor Society, 1969 March 19 (Box 44, Folder 59)
      - District 65, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1969 March 22 (Box 44, Folder 60)
      - Holy Name Society, 1969 March 23 (Box 44, Folder 61)
      - Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce Bossirt Hotel, 1969 March 24 (Box 44, Folder 62)
      - Correctional Association of New York, 1969 March 25 (Box 44, Folder 63)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1969 March 26 (Box 44, Folder 64)
      - AUFBAU (an American weekly published in New York City), 1969 March 27 (Box 44, Folder 65)
      - Subway Supervisors Association, 1969 March 28 (Box 44, Folder 66)
      - German Society of New York, 1969 March 29 (Box 44, Folder 67)
      - Association of the Bar, 1969 April 7 (Box 44, Folder 68)